begindot.com 2019-07-29

# Privacy Policy

In the process of using the services of Begindot, contacting us, email subscription you may need to provide personal information like your name, email address, contact no etc. The Personal Information is used for the purposes such as customization of the content you see, to fulfill your requests for certain services, and to contact you about our services.

We never share your personal information with any third party and the user has the option to refuse to supply personally-identifying information to us.

We are committed to protecting the privacy and confidentiality of all Personal Information that you may share as a user in good faith.

Personal Information will be kept confidential and will be used for our research, marketing, analysis objectives and other internal business purposes only.

**Contact Form**

We use WPForms plugin on the contact us page to collect users queries, guest post requests, and advertisement related inquiries. The information collected through to the plugin comes to our email and we use that information only for answering the queries.

**Email Subscription Form**

We are using Mailerlite services for email subscription and marketing. We collect the user’s email ID who wants to receive our updates, offers and blog posts. The collected emails are stored on the Mailerlite site. While we never sell any of the user’s email we don’t have control over the Mailerlite platform.

**Comment Section**

We are using the default WordPress commenting system and if you choose to comment on any of our blog posts, it will need your email ID.

**Analytics**

We are using Google Analytics to track the traffic details on our site. For more details, you can have a look at this page https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites

**Push Notification**

We are using OneSignal for the browser push notification and the system can only push notifications to those who offered us consent to send updates.

**Disclosure**

  * The users’ privacy is very important to us. We do not either sell or rent users’ personal information to third parties without users’ at any point.
  * We may be required from time to time to disclose users’ personal information to Governmental or law enforcing agencies or our regulators, but we will only do so under proper authority.
  * Begindot also reserves the right to make use of the personal information in any investigation or judicial process relating to the fraudulent activity.

**User Responsibility:** You may use personal information gathered from Begindot only to follow up with another user related to a specific posting, do not to send spam or collect personal information from other users without consent.

**Modification of Information:** You can see, modify or erase your personal information on my account status page.

**Confidentiality of Information:**  Begindot users agree and accept that they have been fully informed the use of features may lead to publication, to all users of Begindot.

Users further agree that the authenticity of, and consequences of the posting by users of any personal information about themselves or any other person, are the sole responsibility of the user.

Users further agree and accept that the terms of the Privacy Policy will be applicable to the use of all features, existing and new.

However, the Users agree and accept that confidentiality of information posted on such features has been waived by the Users of such features themselves.

**Data Security:** No data broadcast over the internet can be guaranteed to be completely secure. So while we strive to protect such information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us and you do so at your own risk.

**Content Policy:** Begindot is updated by different authors, the ideas, point of views and all other details mentioned in the site are the author’s own perspective, and the site is not liable for any kind of financial or non-financial loss that may be faced by any user.

### Cookie Policy

When you visit Begindot, cookies can be stored on your computer. Cookies are little pieces of information that can help identify your browser and that can store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize webpage content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

**Policy Update:**  Begindot reserves the rights to update & modify the privacy policy time to time whenever required, it is user’s responsibility to check the policy detail & keep informed.

**Affiliate Disclosure:** We often produce content where we are an affiliate to the product and services we write about and earn a commission if you make a purchase any product or service through our link. Begindot takes no responsibility for any fault or non-delivery of product or services you purchase through our like. You are liable to take your own decision before you make the purchase.

Updated 23-05-2018
